[{"answer": "That's my brother.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Who was screaming there, Robert?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I thought it was more of the same that we've seen.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Natalie Jackson, what did you make of the interview I conducted with Robert Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "I mean -- do you believe that the family is conspiring to create a version of events best suited to a defense under the \"Stand Your Ground\" law in Florida?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "His nose is still broken.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Does he have injuries now?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "His nose is still broken, yes.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "It's still broken?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Look, I'm not a doctor.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "We're confident the medical records are going to explain all of George's medical history.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "How do you explain that?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Toure, calm down.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "What are you talking habit?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "One thing I notice is obviously the Zimmerman family is banding together to try to keep George out of jail for the rest of his life.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "And are you abreast of more information than anybody else in America right now?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "That's not the information that I had 30 minutes ago.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Are you aware of that?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "In the first days, in the first weeks of the situation, what many people were doing, what I was trying to do in that was to pile on and to say, hey, look, this guy is not doing the right thing.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "That's a pretty serious responsible piece of journalism, isn't it, Toure?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "You're showing you clearly don't understand the depth of the pain in the American soul that is at play in this situation.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What don't I understand about America?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Do you believe that George Zimmerman murdered Trayvon Martin?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "You asked me what I think.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "You've convicted him?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I don't know how they justify it.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "How can they justify that?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "EINSTEIN: A PG-13 would be 100 percent what we're looking for.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Would that be OK for you?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Well, I think it taps into something.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What is the message that you're really sending with this movie?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "When you she this movie and you see these kids beating each other up, or these kids coming against somebody for there being black, or they don't look the way they're supposed to, or they are gay, or whatever reason, and they get mercilessly beaten up, that's where you draw the line.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Where is that line, do you think, to be drawn?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Listen, I never bullied anybody in my life.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Are you a changed character, as a leopard changes spots, Harvey?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "This will be my 14th time.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "How many times have you done this?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "CENTIRE: Well, Kitty Wells was queen of country music forever.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Is that who you think?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "If they say they about me, I'll sure take that.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "But are you the current queen?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Kiowa.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Just like you did it.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "How do I pronounce that?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Is it where -- one of those guys?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "It's the people.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Because it is a special world, isn't it?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Is it part of the territory, do you think?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Horrible.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "I just want to ask you what effect that had on your life afterwards, how it changed your outlook on life, to lose so many people that you were so close to in one horrible day?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "It is very true.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "A cliched thing to say, but it's often true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "CENTIRE: Yeah.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Second time around better?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "The thing I learned about me is that I need to communicate more.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "What did you learn, A, about you as a wife, and B, about the kind of husband that best suited you?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Oh yes, no talk.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Yes, I could go three days sulking up.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Three days?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "To be a successful wife?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, everywhere.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Is there much call for country music in Malibu?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120330pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Will you be singing?", "qSentId": 677}]